<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Seattle Spot Hunter</string>
    <string name="title_activity_maps">Seattle Spot Hunter</string>
    <string name="spot1name">Space Needle</string>
    <string name="spot1desc">Iconic, 605-ft.-tall spire at the Seattle Center, with an observation deck and a rotating restaurant.</string>
    <string name="spot2name">Pike Place Market</string>
    <string name="spot2desc">A public market overlooking the Elliott Bay waterfront. The Market opened August 17, 1907, and is one of the oldest continuously operated public farmers\' markets in the United States.</string>
    <string name="spot3name">Museum of Pop Culture</string>
    <string name="spot3desc">Inspired by Jimi Hendrix, the museum includes items from icons ranging from Bo Diddley to Bob Dylan.</string>
    <string name="spot4name">Chihuly Garden and Glass</string>
    <string name="spot4desc">Art museum and sculpture garden showcasing Dale Chihuly\'s large, colorful glass works.</string>
    <string name="spot5name">Seattle Art Mueseum</string>
    <string name="spot5desc">This roomy space hosts special exhibits and a permanent collection of both current and classic artworks.</string>
    <string name="spot6name">Kerry Park</string>
    <string name="spot6desc">Panoramic views of Downtown and the Space Needle draw visitors to this small neighborhood park.</string>
    <string name="spot7name">Woodland Park Zoo</string>
    <string name="spot7desc">92-acre zoo with nearly 300 species, a vintage carousel, summer concerts and an indoor play space.</string>
    <string name="spot8name">Seattle Aquarium</string>
    <string name="spot8desc">Popular spot for families offers an underwater viewing dome, coral-reef tank, otters and a touch-tank.</string>
    <string name="spot9name">Gas Works Park</string>
    <string name="spot9desc">Former site of an oil plant is now a 20-acre park with picnic facilities and dramatic city views.</string>
    <string name="spot10name">Gum Wall</string>
    <string name="spot10desc">Iconic brick wall covered with chewed-up gum in an alley under Pike Place Market.</string>
    <string name="spot11name">Pacific Science Center</string>
    <string name="spot11desc">Rotating science exhibits plus laser light shows, a tropical butterfly house and IMAX movie theaters.</string>
    <string name="spot12name">Seattle Great Wheel</string>
    <string name="spot12desc">Giant Ferris wheel offering climate-controlled gondolas and a bird\'s-eye view of the city\'s landmarks.</string>
    <string name="spot13name">Fremont Troll</string>
    <string name="spot13desc">Troll Under the Bridge is an interactive, 6.5-ton, mixed media statue made in 1990 by local artists.</string>
    <string name="spot14name">Golden Gardens Park</string>
    <string name="spot14desc">City park draws outdoor lovers for Puget Sound and mountain views, trails and a dog off-leash area.</string>
    <string name="spot15name">Olympic Sculpture Park</string>
    <string name="spot15desc">An offshoot of the Seattle Art Museum, this park features numerous sculptures spread over 9 acres.</string>
    <string name="spot16name">Washington Park Arboretum | UW Botanic Gardens</string>
    <string name="spot16desc">Jointly managed by the University of Washington Botanic Gardens and the City of Seattle, this 230 acre park contains a dynamic assortment of plants, some found nowhere else in the Northwest.</string>
    <string name="spot17name">Smith Tower</string>
    <string name="spot17desc">Iconic 1914 office tower featuring a speakeasy-style cocktail bar and a 35th-floor observatory.</string>
    <string name="spot18name">University of Washington - Seattle Campus</string>
    <string name="spot18desc">Public University with many interesting locations such as Drumheller Fountain, Suzzalo Library Reading Room, and the UW Cherry Blossom Trees</string>
    <string name="spot19name">Seattle Japanese Gardens</string>
    <string name="spot19desc">3.5-acre formal garden with a cherry orchard, water features and teahouse hosting seasonal ceremonies.</string>
    <string name="spot20name">Coleman Dock</string>
    <string name="spot20desc">While officially known as Pier 52, this dock serves as the Seattle terminal for all Washington State Ferrys to Bainbridge Island and Bremerton</string>
</resources>
